Question!
First time fighting in this terrain
How do you survive?
Defense first!
Get into formation!
Uh-uh!
The best defense?
Don't let the enemy find you
Hehe
This "Druzhna training footage"
Will make me a fortune!
So
If you can hide from me for the next three minutes...
You get double dessert with your next ration!
Uh... Huh?
Let's begin!
Whoooooa!
Out!
You're out!
You're out
Aaaaah!
Out
Found you
Heavy footsteps...
Loud breathing...
When you find the perfect hiding spot
You should ask yourself this
How well hidden am I really?
That's all for today's anti-recon training
Dismissed!
No... No!
These are useless!
What sort of training is this anyway!?
Hello there!
Are you a tourist from abroad?
Or a spy sent by my colleagues...?
I... I'm...
Shh, don't answer that
Watching us from a distance
Must be boring...
Why don't you join in the fun?
You're just going to let her go?
*yawn* She's a small fry
Someone must've paid her
For intel on the Druzhna
...Or dirt, maybe
I'll leave the rest to you
We don't have the time to follow up
More importantly...
She's a pretty good photographer!
I'm going to put these in my album!
Ooh, what a great angle!
And the backdrop looks great!
...But you have time for this?
Ah, and this one's— Huh?
...Hm?
How dare she...
I'm going to stuff her inside a snowman!
...Pfft